Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Supplemental Files, 1952-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Supplemental Files
  - Career Development Fund for Women Faculty 1994-1999
    - 1998
      - Nominees
        - Kasa-Vubu, Josephine (Box 49)
        - Ketefian, Shake (Box 49)
        - Kossoudji, Sherrie (Box 49)
        - Malow, Beth (Box 49)
        - Milroy, Lesley (Box 49)
        - Moroi, Sayoko (Box 49)
        - Nelson, Christine (Box 49)
        - Oswald, Lynda (Box 49)
        - Reuter-Lorenz, Pat (Box 49)
        - Shatz, Marilyn (Box 49)
        - Staples, Loretta (Box 49)
        - Tilbury, Dawn (Box 49)
        - Tosney, Kathryn (Box 49)
        - Walwyn, Karen (Box 49)
    - 1999
      - Awardees
        - Bike, Stacy (Box 49)
        - Brei, Diann (Box 49)
        - Brown, Susan (Box 49)
        - Chen, Serena (Box 49)
        - Chan, Yan (Box 49)
        - Colletti, Lisa (Box 49)
        - Cooney, Kathleen (Box 49)
        - Felt, Barbara True (Box 49)
        - Fuller, A. Oveta (Box 49)
        - Gere, Anne (Box 49)
        - Goldman, Rachel (Box 49)
        - Green, Carmen (Box 49)
        - Hahn, Jessica (Box 49)
        - Hedstrom, Margaret (Box 49)
        - Hunt, Margaret Rose (Box 49)
        - Jacobsen, Carol (Box 49)
        - Johnson, Yuki (Box 49)
        - Keizer, Arlene (Box 49)
        - Kirschner, Denise (Box 49)
        - Kossoudji, Sherrie (Box 49)
        - Lithgow-Bertelloni, Carolina (Box 49)
        - Pass, Helen (Box 49)
        - Ramirez-Christensen, Esperanza (Box 49)
        - Roubidoux, Marilyn (Box 49)
        - Samuelson, Linda (Box 49)
        - Satterfield, Teresa (Box 49)
        - Seasholtz, Audrey (Box 49)
        - Tinkle, Theresa (Box 49)
        - Widner, Jennifer (Box 49)
        - Wooldridge, Margaret (Box 49)
        - Zint, Michaela (Box 49)
      - Nominees
        - Andonyadis, Nephelie (Box 50)
        - Brabec, Elizabeth (Box 50)
        - Burmeister, Margit (Box 50)
        - Castle, Valerie (Box 50)
        - Ekotto, Frieda (Box 50)
        - Guck, Marion (Box 50)
        - Gumucio, Deborah (Box 50)
        - Hubbs, Nadine (Box 50)
        - Isom, Lori (Box 50)
        - Malow, Beth (Box 50)
        - Martyn, Kristy Kiel (Box 50)
        - Milroy, Lesley (Box 50)
        - Murphy, Hedwig (Box 50)
        - Oswald, Lynda (Box 50)
        - Pierce, Penny (Box 50)
        - Robertson, Patricia (Box 50)
        - Root, Terry (Box 50)
        - Simeone, Diane (Box 50)
        - Snow, Sandra (Box 50)
        - Sonnad, Seema (Box 50)
        - Thomas, Pamela (Box 50)
        - Tortora, Christina (Box 50)
        - Velez-Aguayo, Evelyn
  - Presidents' Council of the State Universities of Michigan (PCSUM) 1994-2002
    The Presidents' Council of the State Universities of Michigan (PCSUM), 1994-2002 (9 lin. ft.), serves as a forum for the presidents and chancellors of Michigan's fifteen public universities to discuss and frame positions on key higher education finance and policy issues. Its predecessor, the Michigan Council of State College Presidents was formed in 1952. Representatives from the Provost's Office attended meetings with other universities' representatives to evaluate and approve new academic programs. This series consists largely of the records of these program reviews, proposed by all of Michigan's universities, in numerical order. There are additional records of the PCSUM in the Provost and Vice
    - Program Reviews
      - #758-858 May 1994-June 1995, 42 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #758, BM in Music (Box 51)
            [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
          - #759, BFA in Music (Box 51)
          - #760, BFA in Music (Box 51)
          - #816, PhD Engineering Manufacturing (Box 51)
          - #828, Spin-off Environmental (Box 51)
          - #844, BFA Jazz & Contemporary Improvisation. (Box 51)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - #846, MA Adult Instruction (Box 51)
          - #847, Phase out (Box 51)
        - UM Flint programs
          - #761, Spin-off Non-profit Agency; 778 (Box 51)
          - MS Health Education (Box 51)
          - #779, BS Environmental Health (Box 51)
      - #859-927 May 1995-June 1996, 43 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #879, Grad certificate (Box 52)
          - #893, Culture and cognition (Box 52)
          - #895-896, Spin-offs (Box 52)
          - #897, Athletic training (Box 52)
          - PhD Educational Studies-no formal review (Box 52)
          - #908, Space/planetary physics (Box 52)
          - #909, Certificate in film studies (Box 52)
          - #913, Spin-off Public health genetics. (Box 52)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - #872, MS Auto engineering. (Box 52)
        - UM Flint programs
          - #863-864, 867-871 Spin-offs (Box 52)
          - #875, Spin-off (Box 52)
          - #907, Phase out (Box 52)
      - #928-1008 June 1996-Jan 1997, 32 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #934-935, Recombinations School of Information (Box 53)
          - #940, Spin-off Art (Box 53)
          - #977-981, Recombinations Social Work (Box 53)
          - #982, Financial engineering (Box 53)
          - #993, Spin-off English. (Box 53)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - #930, Non-profit leadership certificate (Box 53)
          - #985, MA Liberal studies (Box 53)
      - #1056-1094 June 1997-February 1998, 38 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #1056, Spin-off Information Human-computer interaction (Box 54)
          - 1077, Spin-off PhD in Information (Box 54)
          - 1078, Spin-off Graduate certificate in cellular biology (Box 54)
          - 1079, MA Music theory (Box 54)
          - 1082, Spin-off BA Music in theatre performance (Box 54)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - 1057, Professional development (Box 54)
        - UM Flint programs
          - 1063, BS Administration of Services to the Aged (Box 54)
          - #1067, BS Radiation therapy (Box 54)
      - #1080, 1095-1154 April 1998-March 1999, 14 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #1105, Women's studies 1115 Spin-off Cognitive sciences (Box 55)
          - #1136, Immunology (Box 55)
          - #1137, Information Economics Management and Policy (Box 55)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - #1102, BS Computer engineering 1113 Spin-off BS Finance (Box 55)
          - #1114, Spin-off BS Information systems (Box 55)
          - #1124, Phase out BS Public Administration (Box 55)
          - #1143, MS Accounting (Box 55)
          - #1144, MS Finance (Box 55)
      - #1148-1229 March 1999-January 2000, 38 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #1156, Spin-off Astronomy and Astrophysics (Box 56)
          - #1157, Spin-off MS Environmental engineering (Box 56)
          - #1173, Applied and Interdisciplinary Math (Box 56)
          - #1174, Industrial ecology certificate (Box 56)
          - #1175, Development, psychopathology and mental health certificate (Box 56)
          - #1171, Women's studies and history (Box 56)
          - #1172, Law and Japanese studies (Box 56)
          - #1195, ME Pharmaceutical Engineering (Box 56)
          - #1196, BFA Illustration (Box 56)
          - #1197, ME Plastics Engineering (Box 56)
          - #1218, Applied remote sensing and geoinformation systems (Box 56)
          - #1219, Construction engineering and management (Box 56)
          - #1220, Naval architecture and marine engineering (Box 56)
          - #1221, Space systems (Box 56)
          - #1222, Certificate in simulation and gaming (Box 56)
          - #1223, Sound recording (Box 56)
          - #1224, Urban design (Box 56)
          - #1225, PhD Linguistics-Germanic languages (Box 56)
          - #1226, PhD Linguistics-Romance languages (Box 56)
          - #1227, PhD Linguistics-Slavic languages (Box 56)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - #1167, MS Software engineering (Box 56)
          - #1164, BS Earth science (Box 56)
          - #1165, BBA Marketing 1166 BBA Workforce management (Box 56)
          - #1203, Applied and computational math (Box 56)
        - UM Flint programs
          - #1191, Criminal justice administration (Box 56)
          - #1192, Reading, language and literature; 1202 Biology (Box 56)
      - #1117, 1230-1303 April 2000-January 2001, 77 folders
        - UM Ann Arbor programs
          - #1250, BSE Biomedical engineering (Box 57)
          - #1251, Russian and eastern European certificate (Box 57)
          - #1252, Bioinformatics (Box 57)
          - #1277, Public policy and social science (Box 57)
          - #1278, Latin American and Caribbean studies certificate (Box 57)
          - #1294, Jazz and Contemplative studies (Box 57)
          - Museum studies program certificate (Box 57)
          - Earth sciences (Box 57)
          - Computer science (Box 57)
        - UM Dearborn programs
          - #1234, MS Information systems and technology (Box 57)
          - #1243, Teaching (Box 57)
          - #1259, Software engineering (Box 57)
          - #1293, Environmental Science (Box 57)
        - UM Flint programs
          - #1244, Molecular biology and biotechnology (Box 57)
          - #1281, Health education (Box 57)
          - #1292, Environmental hazards/risk management) (Box 57)
      - #1304-1364 January 2001-June 2002
        - UM Ann Arbor
          - #1325, Organizational studies (Box 58)
          - #1326, BS Environment (Box 58)
        - UM Dearborn
          - #1324, BA Criminal Justice (Box 58)
        - UM Flint
          - #1310, Joint program in public budgeting (Box 58)
          - #1311, Africana studies certificate (Box 58)
          - #1312 General program in Philosophy with emphasis in ethics, social/political (Box 58)
          - #1357, Doctor of physical therapy (Box 58)
      - #1365-1377 June 2002
        - UM Ann Arbor (Box 59)
          - #1374, Interdisciplinary program in survey methodology certificate (Box 59)
    - Records of Bob Holbrook 1994-1996
      - Admission requirements 1994-1995 (Box 59)
      - Agenda/Minutes 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Membership 1995-1996 (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Shiga Program 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 59)
        (The Japan Center for Michigan Universities)